[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The first professional sports organization in the USA was formed in this city.", "correct_answer": "Baltimore", "incorrect_answers": ["Boston", "Charleston", "Cleveland"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This actor, who starred in the film Marty and on the sitcom McHales Navy, played Duke Engstrom in the movie The Wild Bunch.", "correct_answer": "Ernest Borgnine", "incorrect_answers": ["William Holt", "Ben Ryan", "Kelsey Grammar"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This popular board game is published by Parker Brothers. The board consists of forty spaces containing twenty-eight properties.", "correct_answer": "Monopoly", "incorrect_answers": ["Scrabble", "Trouble", "Sorry!"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What does the term Homo erectus mean?", "correct_answer": "a man who is able to stand upright", "incorrect_answers": ["a creature that has the ability to reason", "a man who can make tools", "a hominid"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Herpetoculture is a hobby related to keeping a collection of what kind of animals?", "correct_answer": "Reptiles", "incorrect_answers": ["Birds", "Cats", "Fish"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "A diet high in sugar and starch has more energy, so people who eat such a diet do not get as hungry as people who eat a diet low in sugar and starch.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which part of the cactus performs the process of photosynthesis?", "correct_answer": "Stem", "incorrect_answers": ["Blooms", "Roots", "Spines"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The oldest male stripper was that old when the record was documented.", "correct_answer": "65", "incorrect_answers": ["78", "101", "54"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "If magma contains more than 65% silica, the lava is called this.", "correct_answer": "felsic or acidic", "incorrect_answers": ["thick", "mafic or basic", "dense"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In what year did the movie American Pie hit the theaters?", "correct_answer": "1999", "incorrect_answers": ["1997", "1998", "2000"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Echidnas can swim.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Sharks can have up to nine gills on each side of their body.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}]